嘿  老爸  今天过得怎么样
Hey, Dad. How was your day?
你真想知道
Do you really want to know?
事实上  我只是出于礼貌
Actually, I was just being polite.
简直糟透了
It was horrible!
哦  好吧  看来不管怎样你都要和我说了
Oh, good. So you're gonna tell me anyway.
托比害的我整晚没睡  我今天跟个僵尸一样
Toby kept me awake all night, so I was a zombie all day.
你知道吗  我都累糊涂了
You know, I was so tired
都把白蚁喷雾往一窝老鼠洞里喷了
I used termite spray on a nest full of rats.
呃  你可以  嗯
Well.. You'll uh..
你可以明天再杀死他们  哈  老爸
You'll kill them tomorrow, huh, Dad?
我总是不知道该说什么
I never know what to say.
噢  不  你知道吗
Oh, no. You know what?
我想我只是需要在这儿躺上一会儿
I think I'm just gonna lay down right here.
噢耶
Oh yeah.
托比  够了
Toby, come on..
好好配合我  行不行
Work with me here. Please?
帮帮你老妈吧
Help a mother out.
你猜谁中午又没睡
Guess who missed his nap?
再猜猜谁睡得特别好
And guess who took an extra long one?
告诉你
Check it out.
我刚刚加入了游行乐队
I just joined the marching band.
盖比  盖比
Gabe! Gabe!
盖比
Gabe!
- 怎么了  - 把这玩意儿拿出去
- What?  - Take it outside.
不是吧  达布尼太太刚刚让我拿进来
No, Mrs. Dabney just told me to take it inside.
亲爱的  亲爱的  这里有PJ的一些邮件
Honey? Honey? Here's some mail for PJ.
你明天能不能送到他的公寓里
Maybe you could take it to his apartment tomorrow?
- 我现在去送怎么样  - 好极了
- How about if I do it now?  - Okay.
演奏棒极了  等一下  我去拿我的指挥棒
This is so great. Hang on. I'll get my baton.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast</i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late and Dad jokes.</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"</i>
■
翻译： 寂_翼  Tracy
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite.</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof.</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I survived.</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice.</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right.</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down.</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around.</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十二集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E12  T. Wrecks
嘿  谢谢你来看我的排球赛
Hey, thanks for coming to my volleyball game.
不用客气  我很荣幸
Oh yeah. My pleasure.
能看见那么多的帅小伙
Getting to see all those cute guys
穿着紧身衣服和短裤跑来跑去
running around in tight shirts and shorts.
但是我通常只关注着你
But mostly you. I focused on you.
是的  比赛简直棒极了
Well, it was an awesome game.
跟你说吧  这支球队今年是真的团结成一体了
I'm telling you, the team's really coming together this year.
哇  那作为其中的一份子一定超级有趣
Yeah? Yeah, it must be really fun to be a part of a team.
你知道我有多悲剧吗
You know what's kind of sad?
这是我高中的最后一年而我却从来没有打过体育比赛
This is my last year of high school and I've never played a sport.
这样啊
Oh well.
我想到了  我要加入女子排球队
You know what? I'll join the girls' volleyball team.
你要去打排球  知道吗  排球没那么容易
You're gonna play volleyball? Look, it's not that easy.
嗯  又能有多难呢  你都会打
Well, how hard could it be? You do it.
这非常难  好吗  我只是让它看起来比较容易
It's very difficult, all right? I just make it look easy.
和做你男朋友有异曲同工之妙
Kind of like being your boyfriend.
噢  噢  噢
Oh oh oh!
噢  帅啊  一整天了
Oh, yes! All day long!
我来开门
I got it.
- 嘿  - 嘿  老爸
- Hey.  - Hey, Dad.
欢迎来到PJ和埃米特的小屋
Welcome to Casa De PJ and Emmett.
什么  等等  我们不是应该叫做
What? Wait, I thought we were calling it
“埃米特和PJ的奇妙世界”吗
"Emmett and PJ's World O' Fun"?
所以  你来这个名字未定的地方做什么呢
So, what brings you to our place to be named later?
我给你送来了一些邮件  嘿  椅子不错
I brought you some mail. Hey! You got chairs.
哦  耶
Oh, yeah.
与架子鼓和哭闹孩子的小屋真是天壤之别啊
Quite the change from Casa De Drums and Screaming Kids.
噢  我们还是“奇妙世界”吧  “小屋”已经被他们用了
Oh, let's go with "World O' Fun, they're already using "Casa De".
你知道的  邓肯叔叔  这里并不总是这么安静
You know, it's not always this quiet here, Mr. Duncan.
我们就在火车站边上  常常听见警笛声
We're right next door to a fire station, so we get a lot of sirens.
那么  警笛会半夜因为肚子饿就每小时响一次吗
So, does a siren go off every hour of the night because it's hungry?
警笛需要帮助打嗝和换尿布吗
Does a siren need to be burped and changed?
您不知道什么是警笛  是吧
You don't know a lot about sirens, do you?
好吧  老爸  嗯  谢谢拜访
Well, Dad, um, thanks for stopping by.
那个  嗯
It, uh..
老爸
Dad?
我想他睡过去了
I think he's asleep.
而且他坐在遥控器上  我们要怎么换台
And he's sitting on the remote. How are we gonna change the channel?
- 我有主意了  - 什么
- I got an idea.  - What's that?
嗯
Uh..
- 成功了  - 非常好
- It worked.  - Okay.
- 等等  等等  上一个  - 哦  嗯
- Wait, wait, wait, go back.  - Oh um.
- 啊  - 完美
- Ah.  - Perfect.
好的
Okay.
现在我们该怎么调大音量呢
Now how are we gonna turn up the volume?
- 音量正好  - 没错
- Volume's fine.  - Yup.
嘿  老妈  我的科学作业需要找人帮忙
Hey, Mom? I need some help with my science project.
老爸呢
Where's Dad?
嗯  看这儿
Uh, hello?
为什么不找我来帮忙
Why don't you want my help?
别这样  盖比  我超擅长科学的
Come on, Gabe. I'm great at science.
听起来多有趣啊
And it sounds like fun.
你觉得帮我完成科学作业听起来有趣
Helping me with a science project sounds fun?
宝宝吐了我得处理一下  过来  帮我忙
I'm covered in spit-up. Work with me, here.
好吧  我可以让你试试
All right. I'll give you a shot.
很好
Great.
我们先讲清楚  我可不会上当替你做所有作业
And just so we're clear, I'm not gonna let you trick me
别拿忽悠你爸的那一套对付老娘
into doing all the work like you do with Dad.
告诉你吧  老爸被忽悠得乐在其中呢
For your information, Dad enjoys being tricked.
这是我们一贯的相处方式
It's part of the dance we do.
好吧  作业是什么
All right, what's the project?
建造一艘模型火箭在科学博览会上发射用
Building a model rocket to launch at the science fair.
哦哦  好有趣
Ooh. Fun.
- 什么时候截止  - 两天后
- When's it due?  - Two days.
两天后
Two days?!
你为什么要等到最后一刻才做作业
Why did you wait until the last minute?
呃  这时候老爸工作效率最高
Well, that's when Dad does his best work.
这倒是真的
That's true.
各位  听好了
Listen up, everybody.
来见见我们队最新加入的成员
I want you to meet the newest member of our team.
- 嗨  大家好  我是泰迪  - 错
- Hi, everybody. I'm Teddy.  - Wrong.
不  我很确定
No, I'm pretty sure.
泰迪太软弱了  太温和了
Teddy's too soft. It's too nice.
现在起  你的排球队名字叫  嗯
From now on, your volleyball name is uh..
霸王龙
T-Rex!
伸展一下  我去拿一个新哨子来
Keep stretching. I'm gonna get a fresh whistle.
教练喜欢给我们起个凶猛的恐龙外号
Coach likes to give us all fierce dinosaur nicknames
用我们名字的首字母开头
that go with the first letter of our name.
我叫翁妮  所以我的外号是“迅猛龙”
I'm Vonnie, so I'm "Velociraptor,"
史蒂芬妮是“剑龙”
Stephanie's "stegosaurus,"
泰勒是“翼龙”
Taylor's "pterodactyl".
但是翼龙的首字母是P
But pterodactyl begins with a "P".
跟教练说去  他可喜欢被挑错了
Tell it to the coach. He loves to be corrected.
好的  我们开始吧
All right, let's get to work.
不好意思  我以为你会去接那个球
I'm sorry, I thought you were gonna get that.
好  杀得漂亮  这球太棒了
Way to go. Nice shot. That was awesome.
噢  你还好吗
Oh, are you okay?
那球该我接的  是吗
That was mine, wasn't it?
就这样吧  练习结束
That's it. Practice is over.
你留下  霸王龙
Except for you, T-Rex.
我要和你私下谈谈
I want to talk to you in private.
你这个废物
You stink.
教练  我想我们还不是私下
Coach, I don't think we're in private yet.
你知道为什么说你是废物吗
And do you know why you stink?
不知道
No.
我没想让你回答我的问题  明白吗
When I ask a question, I don't want an answer, do you understand me?
我不知道该做什么
I don't know what to do.
你太善良了
You're too nice.
人善被人欺  马善被人骑
Nice people, they get pushed around.
我说的可不是排球  我说的是人生
And I'm not talking about volleyball, I'm talking about life.
- 我才第一天来  - 也可能是你的最后一天
- It's just my first day.  - And possibly your last.
现在  如果你还想在我的队里待下去
Now, if you want to stay on my team,
你明天再来得干点刺激的事
you need to come back tomorrow and play with some fire.
- 明白了吗  - 明白了
- You got it?  - Got it.
哦  还有件事
Oh, and one more thing.
翼龙的首字母其实是P
Pterodactyl actually starts with a "P".
我知道这很容易弄混  但是
I know that it's kind of confusing, but it's..
给我出去
Get out of here!
你看  一起做作业的感觉很好吧
See? Isn't this nice? Working on a project together.
何止是好  简直棒极了  完全不像在做家庭作业
Nice? It's great. It doesn't even feel like homework.
就像是  家庭游戏  家庭娱乐之类的
It's more like... home play, or home joy, or...
太过了
Too much?
好吧
Okay.
嘿  小查莉  你想要什么
Hey, Charlie. What do you want?
噢
Oh..
我完全忘记了  我答应查莉和她一起玩的
I forgot, I totally promised Charlie I was gonna play with her.
亲爱的查莉  很抱歉我不能陪你玩了
Charlie, I'm sorry I can't play with you.
听着  我知道托比出生后
Look, I know you've been feeling neglected
你一直有种被忽视的感觉
ever since Toby came along,
但是我正和妈妈一起做一项重要的学校作业
but I'm working on a big school project with Mom.
哦  算了  去和她玩上几分钟吧
Oh, you know, go play with her for a few minutes.
这东西我先做着就行了
I'll just get this started.
那就听你的
If you say so.
我的玩具呢
Where's my toy?
- 就像我们说好的那样  - 谢谢你
- Just like we talked about.  - Thank you.
好了  我们现在去地下室吧
All right, now, let's head down to the basement
你去那儿玩“安静地坐着”
where you're gonna play "sit quietly,"
我去玩“看电视”
while I play "watch TV".
然后他说我是废物  就因为我太善良了
And then he said that I stink because I'm too nice.
- 你要知道都是你的错  - 怎么会是我的错
- You know this is all your fault.  - How is it my fault?
是你自己要加入体育队的
You're the one who wanted to join a team.
你该告诉我教练是个疯子的
Well, you could have mentioned that the coach was a lunatic.
你知道吗  我已经受够了  我要退出
You know what? I don't need this. I'm gonna quit.
好吧  我以为你真心想要运动的
Well, I thought you wanted to play a sport.
当然  反正还有很多别的运动嘛
Yeah, well there's plenty of other sports out there.
我可以参加那项  呃
I'll do the one with the, um...
有球还有棍子还有头盔的运动
With the the ball and the stick and the helmet.
好吧  那你是要参加垒球  曲棍球  还是长曲棍球
Okay, so that would be either Softball, Field Hockey, or Lacrosse.
- 哪个是在户外的  - 都是
- Which one's outdoors?  - All of them are.
- 哪个服装最可爱  - 都不
- Which one has the cutest uniforms?  - None of them do.
运动太难了
Sports is so hard.
- 先生们  - 老爸
- Gentlemen.  - Hey, Dad.
- 你有什么事  - 需要再次来访
- What are you doing here?  - Again?
哦  我  呃  给你们带来了点有家庭温情的小礼物
Oh, I, uh.. Brought you a little housewarming gift.
真空包装袋
Vacuum bags.
如果我们有个真空吸尘器  这会派上用场的
That will come in handy once we get a vacuum.
那个  老爸  很高兴你来  脱下外套在这待着
Well, Dad, it was nice of you to... Take off your coat and stay.
我还带了
I also brought..
棒极了的日本怪兽电影
This awesome Japanese monster movie.
每次我在家里看他们你老妈都会不高兴
Your Mom hates it when I watch these at home.
快放到电视里
Put it in the thing.
嗯  老爸  你知道的  事实上 我们挺忙的
Um.. You know, actually, Dad, we're kind of busy.
没关系 不用担心 你们不会吵到我的
That's all right. Don't worry about it. You're not gonna bother me.
东京又迎来了美好的一天  是不
Just another peaceful day in Tokyo, huh?
但是马上就要变了哦
Oh, that's gonna change.
泰迪  你怎么下班回家这么晚
Teddy? Why are you getting home from work so late?
那个  我今天在图书馆特别辛苦
Well, I had a very stressful day at the library.
一个老主顾一直在说话  我应该阻止她的
One of the patrons was talking, and I was gonna say something,
但是我不想那么刻薄
but I didn't want to be mean.
于是老板对我发火了  我就躲在书架中间偷偷落泪
Then my boss got mad at me, so I hid in the stacks and cried.
泰迪  你不能这样由着大家欺负你
Teddy, you gotta stop letting people walk all over you.
- 嗯  - 还站在这干嘛
- Yeah. - What are you standing there for?
- 快去厨房做饭  - 是
- Get in the kitchen and make dinner. - Yes, Sir.
先去开门
Get the door first.
- 哈姆斯通老师  - 看看你
- Mr. Hammerstone? - Look at you.
既然你退出了球队  你的余生就任人欺负吧
Because you quit the team, people walked all over you the rest of your life.
我就说吧  我就说吧  我就说吧
I told you so. I told you so. I told you so.
能用下你家厕所么
Can I use your bathroom?
- 可以  - 我就说吧
- Sure. - I told you so.
到此为止  我不要再当老好人了
That's it. I am done being nice.
喔
Aw.
不许这样
No!
亲爱的  睡得好吗
Hey, honey. How'd you sleep?
很糟糕  如果我口气听上去不友好  很遗憾
Lousy. And if that doesn't sound nice, then too bad.
矮油  有人心情不好
Well, someone's in a mood.
你想找茬吗
Got a problem with that?
泰迪  亲爱的  你没事吧
Um, Teddy? Sweetheart, um, are you okay?
因为你看上去  怎么说呢  跟以前判若两人
Because you just seem, I don't know, completely different?
咋滴  是逼我发火吗
What? Do you want some of this?
再给老娘说一次试试
Come again?
我意思是  不管你逼不逼我
Well, you know whether or not you want it..
我都不会发火
I'm not going to give it to you.
不出所料啊
That's what I thought.
盖比  亲
Gabe, honey?
下面要说的话我之前从未对你说过
I'm gonna say something to you I have never said before.
就目前而言  你是我最喜欢的孩子
Right now, you're my favorite.
感觉挺好
Feels good.
我不会经常说这话的
Don't get used to it.
- 嘿  - 爸
- Hey. - Dad.
你是怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
锁匠让我进来的啊
Locksmith let me in.
他在没有我们准许的情况下就让你进来了
He let you into our apartment without our permission?
锁匠和除虫师是兄弟嘛
Locksmiths and exterminators are brothers.
我们的关系就像警察和消防队员
Yeah, we're like cops and firefighters.
只是没他们那么英雄主义
Just a little less heroic.
那啥  我给你们带礼物来了
Hey, you know what? I got you a present.
不用谢哈
And you're welcome.
真空吸尘器
A vacuum cleaner.
好耶
Yay.
我说老爸  你在这待多久了
Uh, so.. Dad, um, how much longer are you..
稍等  披萨好了
Oh. Wait. Pizza's ready.
- 你得把他弄走  - 别担心  他不会在这待很久
- You've gotta get rid of him. - Don't worry. He.. He won't stay long.
听着  我正考虑给你俩弄张沙发床
You know what? I was thinking about getting you guys a sofa bed.
如果我在这待得晚了方便你们留我在这住
You know, so that when I'm here late and you want me to stay over?
现在就弄走
Now.
有办法了
Got an idea.
他喜欢待在这儿是因为这儿安静  对不
So, he likes it here because it's quiet, right?
- 没错  - 看我的
- Right. - Watch this.
- 嘿  老爸  - 嗯
- Hey, Dad? - Yeah?
不介意我试下这个新吸尘器吧
Mind if I take the new vacuum for a little test run?
尽管试
Go ahead.
好的
Okay.
运气太差  竟然是静音的
Just my luck.. The "shush vac".
呃  PJ  你在干嘛
Um, PJ? What are you doing?
啥玩意啊  PJ
What? PJ?
PJ
P.. PJ.
PJ!
啥事啊  老爸
Yes, Dad?
你干啥呢
What are you doing?
不发出那声音我就没有打扫的感觉
Well, I just don't feel like I'm cleaning unless I hear that sound.
吵到你了吗
Is.. Is that bothering you?
没  还是比家里安静
No. Still quieter than home.
啊
Ah.
妈
Mom.
你把我的火箭怎么了
What did you do to my rocket?
首先  这是我建造的
Well, uh, first, I built it.
其次  我把它装饰得美美的
And then I made it purty.
羽毛  怎么还加上羽毛了呢
Feathers? Why'd you have to add feathers?
噢  那是查莉的独特风格
Oh, that was Charlie's special touch.
我们给它命名为
We also named it. Say hello..
彩虹阳光
To "Rainbow Sunshine".
我可不要把这玩意带到学校
I can't take that to school.
那你应该自己装饰
Well, I guess you could always redecorate it yourself.
你是说
You mean..
做我自己的作业
Work on my own project?
真得如此吗
Has it really come to that?
恐怕是这样
I'm afraid so.
这过程真不错啊
It was a good run.
邓肯  我没想到你还会回来
Duncan. I didn't think you'd come back.
仔细思考我说的话了吗
Did you sleep on what I said?
嗯  我日有所思  夜有所梦  仔细思考并深刻咀嚼了
Oh, I slept on it, dreamt it, chewed it up, and spit it out.
好的  恐龙战队  各位听好了
All right, Dinos, listen up.
我们今天要跟男队混战
We're gonna scrimmage the boys' team today.
耶
Yeah!
管它混战是啥意思  尽管来吧
Whatever scrimmage means, bring it!
我还以为你退出了呢
Thought you were quitting.
咋  你想给我洗脑啊
What? You're trying to get in my head?
你是害怕输给一群姑娘吗
Or you afraid to lose to a bunch of girls?
你跟你男友说话口气好呛啊
You trash talk your boyfriend?
我学会了也要那么跟我男友说话
I'm so gonna do that as soon as I learn how to trash talk..
- 等我先找到男友的  - 很好
- And get a boyfriend. - Oh yeah.
运气不错啊  小子
Got lucky, punks.
哦  亲爱的
Oh, sweetums! Oh.
我鼻子被你打断了
I think you broke my nose.
霸王龙  让我来看看
T-Rex, let me get in there.
嗷
Oh!
我的鼻子
Oh, my nose!
我鼻子也被你撞断了
She broke my nose too.
对不起  我不是  是意外
Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't.. It was an accident.
你俩都是意外
They were both accidents.
亲娘啊  我一手打造了一个怪物
Sweet mother, I created a monster!
别啊  伙计们  我不是怪物
No. Guys, come on. I'm not a monster.
我不是怪物
I'm not a monster.
有人知道曲棍球选拔赛啥时候开始不
Does anyone know when Field Hockey try-outs are?
好了
All right.
不错
我完工了
All right, I'm done!
快过来
Come on.
- 哇  - 你觉得咋样啊
- Wow. - What do you think?
你毁了它
You ruined it.
现在的彩虹阳光应该叫
Rainbow Sunshine is now..
黑夜恐怖末日导弹火球
"Black Night Doom Missile Terror Fireball".
好了  我们来试飞一下
All right, let's do a test launch.
等等  在开始之前  我先讲两句
Okay, whoa. Before you do, I've prepared a few words.
晕呐
Oh boy.
远古时代  人类就仰望天空  说
"From the beginning of time, man looked to the heavens and said..
蠢鸟  凭啥它们能飞我们就不能
'Stupid birds! How come they get to fly and we don't?'"
- 我要发射了  - 别别别
- I'm pushing the button. - No, no, no!
我还没念到最精彩的部分呢  等等啊
I haven't gotten to my favorite part. Wait, wait, wait.
三  二  一
Three, two, one..
发射
Blast off.
好一个火球啊
Yeah, that's some fireball.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你在外面干嘛呢
What are you doing out here?
我想和您谈谈
Uh, we need to talk.
好啊  咱进屋谈呗
Okay, but can we do it over at your place?
我在里面感觉更舒服
Because I'm way more comfortable over there.
那啥
Actually..
我们还是就在这谈吧
Actually, let's do it here. Okay?
好吧
Okay.
咳  还真不好开口  我
Wow, this is really hard. I..
真是没法说出口啊
Don't really know how to do this.
不好说的话  就说快点
Well, PJ, if it's hard to say, just say it fast.
跟撕绷带原理一样
It's like.. Like tearing off a bandage.
好吧
All right.
那我说了啊
Here goes.
我不喜欢你老来我这
Idon'twantyoutohangoutatmyplacesomuch.
你能不能稍微再撕慢点
You might want to tear that a little slower.
我
I..
- 不喜欢  - 稍微  再快一点
- Don't.. - Little little.. Little faster.
我不喜欢你老来我这
I don't want you to hang out at my place so much.
对不起老爸  我从家里搬出来
Look, I'm sorry, Dad, but I moved out of
为的就是过我自己的生活
the house so I could be on my own.
你老在那待着吧  就不算我自己的生活了
Kind of hard to do that when you're always there.
我明白了
I see.
你生气了
You mad at me?
没有
No.
- 那就好  - 当然没
- Okay. - No.
你说得没错  这是你家
No, come on, you're absolutely right. It's your place.
你不希望看到你家老头老在这晃悠
You don't want your old man hanging out there all the time.
可不是嘛
No, I do not.
我意思是  意思是
I mean.. I mean..
谢谢您的理解
Thanks for understanding.
哎  我会想念这里的
Oh, I'm gonna miss your place.
我跟你说哈
Because let me tell you something.
就这儿吧
Around here?
我总感觉会有疯狂的事情发生
It always feels like there's something crazy going on.
老妈  我感觉我找到了症结所在
Oh. Mom, I think I found the problem.
电线松了
Loose wires.
那就给弄紧呗哥们
Well dude. Stick 'em together.
- 刚刚那个是火箭吗  - 没错
- Was that a rocket? - Yup.
欢迎随时去我家  老爸
Come over any time, Dad.
- 现在如何  - 走吧
- How about now? - Let's go.
嘿  查莉  大新闻哦
Hey, Charlie. So, big news.
看来我能继续留在排球队了呢
Looks like I'm staying on the volleyball team.
那啥  得在他们对体育馆进行轻度维修之后
You know, after they make a few minor repairs to the gym.
说到轻度维修
Speaking of minor repairs.
这就是让老妈帮忙做科学课作业的后果
So this is what happens if you let Mom help you with a school project.
不是我的错好吧
Okay, it was not my fault.
真的吗  盖比说你是这么说的
Really? Because Gabe said you uttered the words..
那就给弄紧呗哥们
"Dude, stick 'em together".
我不记得我这么说过
I don't recall exactly what I uttered.
我已经提醒过你了哈
Okay. Well, consider yourself warned.
如果你以后还是让老妈帮你做科学课作业的话
If you ever allow Mom to help you with a science project..
那就祝你好运啰  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
飞吧  火箭
Fly, rocket.
高飞吧
Fly high.
嘿  老婆
Hey, hon.
老鲍
Bob?
你在这干嘛
What are you doing here?
PJ和埃米特把我撵出来了
Oh, PJ and Emmett kicked me out.
我出来找点安静的空间
So I'm just looking for a little peace and quiet.
那你跟着我干嘛  快给我消失
Well, you're crowding me. Get lost.
我跟着你
I'm crowding you?
在外太空
In outer space?
你起开行不
Oh, would you just leave?
亲爱的  我正漂浮着呢  我又不能控制椅子
Honey, I'm floating. It's not like I can steer the chair.
那我帮你一把
Oh, well let me help you out.
嘿  哇哦
Hey.. Whoa whoa whoa!
飞吧  椅子
Fly chair.
高飞吧
Fly high!